nobelcom.com 2018-08-22

# PRIVACY STATEMENT AND POLICIES

**PRIVACY STATEMENT AND POLICIES**

Thank you for visiting NobelCom, a NobelOne Inc. website. NobelCom is committed to honouring the privacy of our members and visitors.

NobelOne Inc., www.nobelcom.com ("Nobel", "we", or "our"), and its Customers, Partners, Suppliers, and Affiliates recognize and respect the privacy expectations of our customers. The following must be read and assented to for you to use our site. By using the Site, you are stating that you have read and are agreeing to the following:

**Customer Privacy**   
Nobel is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. 

**Information Collected**   
Nobel can collect information from our users at several different points on our web site. We collect, retain, and use information about you for the purpose of administering our relationship with you. In order to administer our relationship with you, it is necessary for you to provide certain information upon using portions of our Site. Such information includes your name (either your name, company, or organizations name), address, phone number, e-mail address, and other information gathered through the applicable process. 

**Information Automatically Placed On Your Hard Drive (Cookies)**   
In order to provide service to you, we require that a cookie be transferred to your computer's hard disk for record keeping purposes. The Cookies capture your e-mail address and your first and last name. Cookies allow you to access our site easier by storing your password on your computer so that you do not have to enter your password each time you log onto our site. To gain access to our Site, your computer must accept Cookies. 

**Non-Personally-Identifiable Information Collected Automatically (IP Addresses)**   
We collect IP addresses. Collection of IP addresses allows us to monitor fraud on our Site. 

**Children**   
Nobel has no intention of collecting personally identifiable information (name, address, telephone number, or e-mail address) from individuals under the age of eighteen. If a child has provided us with personally-identifiable information, a parent or guardian of that child should contact us at [help@nobelcom.com](mailto:help@nobelcom.com) if they would like the information deleted from our records. We will use reasonable efforts to delete the information regarding the child from our files. 

**Accuracy of Information Collected**   
We continually strive to maintain accurate and complete information about our users, members, customers, and clients. Should you believe that information is inaccurate or incomplete, you should notify [help@nobelcom.com](mailto:help@nobelcom.com) with concerns and the accurate information. We will use reasonable efforts to correct the incorrect information. 

**Security**   
We maintain security measures to protect your information from loss, misuse and alteration of information under our control. Our site employs SSL 256 bit encryption when private information is passed from you to us. The level of encryption you ultimately obtain is dependent upon your browser's capabilities. If you have any questions about security at our web site, please send an email to: [help@nobelcom.com](mailto:help@nobelcom.com)

**Sharing of Information**

**a) Inside Nobel**   
Within Nobel, any employee access to customer information is for business purposes only and is based on a need to know basis. This information is shared with Affiliates so that we can provide services and products that meet your circumstances and needs. 

**b) With Third Parties**   
We enter into agreements with outside companies to provide services to our users. When we enter into such agreements, we require that these companies adhere to the same strict privacy standards in regards to the security and confidentiality of your information. We also do not allow such third party companies to disseminate your information to any other party. 

**c) With Unaffiliated Third Parties**   
As a service to our users, we partner with unaffiliated third parties to offer products and services. At no time is your confidential information provided to these third parties. 

**d) Legally Required Disclosure**   
There may be occasions where we are legally required to disclose information about you, such as in response to a subpoena, to prevent fraud, or to comply with a legally permitted inquiry by a governmental agency. 

**Opt In/Out**   
Our site provides an opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about you. Further, by not opting-out at the applicable places, you are opting-in to our use of your private information as laid out in this privacy statement and policy. By checking the box corresponding to "I agree to receive Email notifications from Nobel", you explicitly give us your express prior authorization to send you e-mail communications. If you choose to opt-in you will receive an e-mail with information of your account.. You can opt-out of receiving e-mail communications, at anytime, by using the unsubscribe mechanism described in each e-mail, by sending an e-mail at [help@nobelcom.com](mailto:help@nobelcom.com)

**Link To This Site**   
If you linked to this site from another site, use of that site is subject to the privacy statement and policies of that site. 

**Link To Other Site**   
This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that Nobel is not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this   
_Note: Use of this Site constitutes consent to monitoring. All web site traffic on this site is monitored for copyright, security, and statistical purposes. Unauthorized attempts to upload or change information, to download the entire web site, or otherwise cause damage are strictly prohibited and may be punishable under any applicable local, state, federal, and/or international laws._

**Why We Collect Information**   
We rely on a number of legal bases to collect, use, share, and otherwise process the information we have about you for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy, including: 

  * As necessary to provide the Services and fulfil our obligations pursuant to the Terms of Service;
  * Where you have consented to the processing, which you can revoke at any time. For example, you may consent to the processing of phone contacts information;
  * Where necessary to comply with a legal obligation, a court order, or to exercise and defend legal claims;
  * To protect your vital interests, or those of others, such as in the case of emergencies;
  * Where you have made the information public;
  * Where necessary in the public interest; and
  * Where necessary for the purposes of Nobel's or a third party's legitimate interests, such as those of visitors, members or partners.
  * To prevent and protect against malicious activity.

**Our Legitimate Interests**   
We process your information in furtherance of our legitimate interests, including: 

  * Providing and improving the Services, including any personalized Services. We do so as it is necessary to pursue our legitimate interests of providing and developing innovative and tailored offerings to our members on a sustained basis; and
  * Keeping the Services safe and secure. We do so as it is necessary to pursue the legitimate interests of Nobel and its members in ensuring the Services are secure, and to protect against fraud, spam and abuse, etc.

**Information Use**   
Nobel may use the information we collect from and about you for any of the following purposes: 

  * To fulfil orders, provide service and communicate with customers;
  * To develop new products or services;
  * To respond to your inquiries;
  * To provide you with customized Service content, targeted offers, and advertising on the Service or on other sites;
  * To contact you with information, newsletters and promotional materials from Nobel or on behalf of our partners and affiliates;
  * To contact you when necessary;
  * To review the usage and operations of our Service and improve our content, products and services;
  * To address problems with the Service or our business;
  * To manage our telecommunications networks;
  * To protect the security or integrity of the Service and our business;
  * As described to you at the point of data collection; and
  * To use and disclose your credit/debit card information only to process payments and prevent fraud.

**Eu Members Rights**   
If you are habitually located in the European Union, you have the right to access, rectify, download or erase your information, as well as the right to restrict and object to certain processing of your information. While some of these rights apply generally, certain rights apply only in certain limited circumstances. We describe these rights below: 

**Access and Porting**   
You can access much of your information by logging into your account. If you require additional access, or if you are not a Nobel client, or if you want to receive a copy of your data, please contact us at [help@nobelcom.com](mailto:help@nobelcom.com). 

**Rectify, Restrict, Limit, Delete**   
You can also rectify, restrict, limit or delete much of your information by logging into your account. If you are unable to do this, please contact us at [help@nobelcom.com](mailto:help@nobelcom.com). 

**Object**   
Where we process your information based on our legitimate interests explained above, or in the public interest, you can object to this processing in certain circumstances. In such cases, we will cease processing your information unless we have compelling legitimate grounds to continue processing or where it is needed for legal reasons. 

**Revoke Consent**   
Where you have previously provided your consent, such as to permit us to process data about you, you have the right to withdraw your consent to the processing of your information at any time. You can do this from the app, or in case you are not able to do it yourself, please contact us at [help@nobelcom.com](mailto:help@nobelcom.com). Revoking permissions, may cause the application to malfunction and no earnings will be shared with you . In certain cases, we may continue to process your information after you have withdrawn consent if we have a legal basis to do so or if your withdrawal of consent was limited to certain processing activities.
